<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.1.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://www.auraimmigration.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://www.auraimmigration.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-02-19T19:13:13+05:30</updated><id>https://www.auraimmigration.com/</id><title>Immigration Consulting</title><subtitle>Immigration Consulting</subtitle><author><name>AuraImmigration</name><email>support@auraimmigration.com</email></author><entry><title>Learn How GST Affects You</title><link href="https://www.auraimmigration.com/blog/2017/11/10/how-gst-affects-you.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Learn How GST Affects You" /><published>2017-11-10T07:09:14+05:30</published><updated>2017-11-10T07:09:14+05:30</updated><id>https://www.auraimmigration.com/blog/2017/11/10/how-gst-affects-you</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.auraimmigration.com/blog/2017/11/10/how-gst-affects-you.html">&lt;p&gt;Since July 2017, India has been set on GST mode, which enables the taxpayers to pay a single tax instead of multiple indirect taxes. This new indirect tax regime,termed as Goods and Services Tax, has been seen a much awaited reform since independence, which subsumes around a dozen of taxed levied by the central and the state governments. As for taxpayers, this tax is expected to affect their daily life positively in the long run. For instance, it leads to significant reduction in the variety of taxes for businesses, as they have to pay lesser rates and exemptions through a comparably simpler tax regime. 
&lt;!--more--&gt;
For startups and small businesses, GST billing has emerged as a ray of respite from the taxes. In the earlier system, a business having more than RS 5 lakh as annual turnover was required to pay Value Added Tax (VAT). However, under GST, this threshold amount has been replaced by 20 lakhs, which exempts many small businesses as well as startups. Even for turnovers between 20 to 50 lakhs, the businesses can opt for a composition scheme, which requires them to pay nominal tax.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GST has also helped logistic industries appreciably in minimizing their operating costs. It has replaced the earlier system where the businesses from this industry has to keep record of multiple warehouses across different states, to avoid paying current CST and state entry taxes during inter-state movement. As for hotel industry, budget hotels, having room tariffs under Rs 1000 are expected to gain heavily with the introduction of GST billing, as they do not require to pay taxes. The GST however increases with the rise in tariff slabs, with a maximum 28% tax being levied on rooms with tariffs more than Rs 7500.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feel free to download our software and ease out your GST tax return process.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>AuraImmigration</name><email>support@auraimmigration.com</email></author><category term="GST" /><category term="Tax" /><category term="GST Billing" /><summary>Since July 2017, India has been set on GST mode, which enables the taxpayers to pay a single tax instead of multiple indirect taxes. This new indirect tax regime,termed as Goods and Services Tax, has been seen a much awaited reform since independence, which subsumes around a dozen of taxed levied by the central and the state governments. As for taxpayers, this tax is expected to affect their daily life positively in the long run. For instance, it leads to significant reduction in the variety of taxes for businesses, as they have to pay lesser rates and exemptions through a comparably simpler tax regime.</summary></entry><entry><title>Get GST-Ready Software Now</title><link href="https://www.auraimmigration.com/blog/2017/10/31/get-gst-ready-software.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Get GST-Ready Software Now" /><published>2017-10-31T07:09:14+05:30</published><updated>2017-10-31T07:09:14+05:30</updated><id>https://www.auraimmigration.com/blog/2017/10/31/get-gst-ready-software</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.auraimmigration.com/blog/2017/10/31/get-gst-ready-software.html">&lt;p&gt;If you are already fed up of filing GST returns on your own and looking for credible assistance to help you out in the accounting and related efforts, the GST-Ready Software is meant exactly for you. It is all engrossed with advanced and utilitarian features that ultimately aim at reducing your paper work significantly. It automated the workflow of your business and lets you keep track of your multiple warehouses collectively. It offers varied GST featured invoices in India, related to sales, purchases, credit notes, debit notes, payment recording, and online payments. 
&lt;!--more--&gt;
The tool is handy in creating, sending and tracking professional GST invoices from anywhere. You can use it to collect payments and even track your inventory per serial number, hence going beyond GST billing. Besides all the regular tasks, our GST ready software performs automatic handling of your accounts whenever your create sale or make purchase. Automatic reminders through email and SMS further intimate your customers hence saving considerable time, enabling you to focus more on your core strength.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other facilities like accessibility, SSL 256 bit encrypted loud infrastructure and data transportation, real-time insightful reports on business performance and advertisement campaigns through CRM are among the other lucrative attractions of this accomplished GST ready software at GInvoicing. So what are you waiting for? Contact us and get registered with us at the earnest.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>AuraImmigration</name><email>support@auraimmigration.com</email></author><category term="GST" /><category term="GST Ready" /><category term="GST Tax" /><summary>If you are already fed up of filing GST returns on your own and looking for credible assistance to help you out in the accounting and related efforts, the GST-Ready Software is meant exactly for you. It is all engrossed with advanced and utilitarian features that ultimately aim at reducing your paper work significantly. It automated the workflow of your business and lets you keep track of your multiple warehouses collectively. It offers varied GST featured invoices in India, related to sales, purchases, credit notes, debit notes, payment recording, and online payments.</summary></entry><entry><title>Learn How GInvoicing Can Help You</title><link href="https://www.auraimmigration.com/blog/2017/10/21/how-ginvoicing-can-help-you.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Learn How GInvoicing Can Help You" /><published>2017-10-21T07:09:14+05:30</published><updated>2017-10-21T07:09:14+05:30</updated><id>https://www.auraimmigration.com/blog/2017/10/21/how-ginvoicing-can-help-you</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.auraimmigration.com/blog/2017/10/21/how-ginvoicing-can-help-you.html">&lt;p&gt;Besides your core competency that works acts as a catalyst in your business growth, we at GInvoicing management are dedicated to help you with you GST related hassles. Considering the intricacies involved in abiding by the GST rules, we assist you with a ready to use GST software that emancipates you with all the involved hassles of GST return filings. With GST transforming the Indian tax regime to the digital front, the need to be technology savvy has become evident. 
&lt;!--more--&gt;
However, even if you possess limited digital awareness, we are there to take up the cudgels in our hand and simplify your task of filing GST returns with ease through our GST ready software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The advanced and robust GInvoicing tool can assist you get started with your GST regime in few simple steps. With the progress in the GST rules, we will also continue to infuse advancements in our software to help you abide by the proceedings quicker and easier. Our GST Invoicing Tool takes care of all your requirements regarding invoicing/billing whether simple or advanced ones, such as those related to multi-tax rates, multi-item, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, it also lets you to manage several GST related obligations like advance receipts, bill of supply GST input tax credit, reverse charge, export invoices, branch transfers, accounting, and so on. Hence, it adapts to your business requirements in entirety and reflects your books of accounts in true sense in the form GST returns. Further, with our software, you can get detect away with any kind of transaction error in real time to make way for accurate GST returns.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>AuraImmigration</name><email>support@auraimmigration.com</email></author><category term="GST" /><category term="GInvoicing" /><category term="GST India" /><summary>Besides your core competency that works acts as a catalyst in your business growth, we at GInvoicing management are dedicated to help you with you GST related hassles. Considering the intricacies involved in abiding by the GST rules, we assist you with a ready to use GST software that emancipates you with all the involved hassles of GST return filings. With GST transforming the Indian tax regime to the digital front, the need to be technology savvy has become evident.</summary></entry><entry><title>Invoice Management</title><link href="https://www.auraimmigration.com/blog/2017/06/14/invoice-management.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Invoice Management" /><published>2017-06-14T17:00:45+05:30</published><updated>2017-06-14T17:00:45+05:30</updated><id>https://www.auraimmigration.com/blog/2017/06/14/invoice-management</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.auraimmigration.com/blog/2017/06/14/invoice-management.html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;invoice-template&quot;&gt;Invoice Template&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GI provides various templates that you can use while creating your invoice. 
&lt;!--more--&gt;
This includes templates for quotes, invoices, emails. Templates allows you to portray information in a sleek and presentable manner so that it is easy for you as well as your clients to understand.
Extending it to further, we have created a brand new template called the Standard – Indian Style template specifically for the Indian consumers. This template include organization name, client name, addresses of both organization and customer, item details, subtotals etc. Currently this template has been added under invoices, in future it will be implemented for estimates.
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/invoice-template.png&quot; alt=&quot;Invoice Template&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;apart-from-this-indian-template-we-already-have-many-other-templates-exists&quot;&gt;Apart from this Indian template, we already have many other templates exists:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Standard Template&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Compact Template&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Continental Template&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Standard – European style Template&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Grand Template&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Standard – Japanese style Template&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Life Template&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Minimalist Template&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Simple Template&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;search&quot;&gt;Search&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ginvoicing has now a search feature that will let you search across your organization. Anything from party, items, estimates, invoices, credit notes, purchase order and expenses can be searched with a few easy clicks.
 No need to dig into individual modules to look for required information any more, head to our brand new search feature, ask for any information and ta-da!
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/search.png&quot; alt=&quot;Search&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;we-are-providing-search-in-collaboration-with-algolia-indexes-you-can-search-based-upon-keywords-in-various-modules-following-modules-are-covered-under-this-new-feature&quot;&gt;We are providing search in collaboration with Algolia indexes. You can search based upon keywords in various modules. Following modules are covered under this new feature:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Party&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Items&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Estimate&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Invoices&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Credit Notes&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Purchase Orders&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Expenses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;User can search on the basis of name, category, unique id, reference numbers, company name, email id etc. When search is successful you will get a matching list, from where you can click and return to the detailed result or click on see more in case there are more match in the result.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this new feature, Search may be your best new accessory. Or at least a useful tool to find information that suits your instant need and even save time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;responsive-user-interface&quot;&gt;Responsive User Interface&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have completely redesigned our GI user interface to make it highly responsive for our users on the go. GI user interface will now be same across any platform whether it be desktops, tablets, or phones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;custom-field&quot;&gt;Custom field&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/custom-field.png&quot; alt=&quot;Custom field&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Extending our invoices usage to next level, we have added custom field to invoices. Currently we are supporting two types of custom field simple text and list. With this user will be able to add custom field to invoices making it more customization and useful as per their requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;enabledisable-custom-fields&quot;&gt;Enable/Disable custom fields.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keeping in view with the custom fields that have been recently added to invoices. Here comes another extension to this existing feature. Users will now have more power to control what should be there on the invoice in terms of custom fields.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>AuraImmigration</name><email>support@auraimmigration.com</email></author><category term="invoice" /><category term="templates" /><category term="GST Formatted" /><summary>Invoice Template
GI provides various templates that you can use while creating your invoice.</summary></entry><entry><title>Inventory Management</title><link href="https://www.auraimmigration.com/blog/2017/06/14/inventory-management.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Inventory Management" /><published>2017-06-14T16:00:33+05:30</published><updated>2017-06-14T16:00:33+05:30</updated><id>https://www.auraimmigration.com/blog/2017/06/14/inventory-management</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.auraimmigration.com/blog/2017/06/14/inventory-management.html">&lt;p&gt;On analyzing and understanding the needs of entrepreneurs, our customers and the ever changing market, we came to know that one of the core foundations of developing a business is proper inventory management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every organization has its own way of managing their inventory. But the process gets harder and becomes more complex as you reach out to more customers and new markets. Hence we here at GI are providing with all new module that will make your inventory management transparent and lucid.
The all new inventory module consist of following sections:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Warehouse&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;New Item interface&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adjustments&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Transfer Order&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Purchase Order&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;warehouse&quot;&gt;Warehouse&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Managing multiple warehouses at one place has never been so easier. GI inventory provides you with a sleek multi-warehouse system  that allows you to track and manage your inventory seamlessly across different locations.
The warehouse module in settings allows you to do the following tasks:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Enable multiple warehouse.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Edit a warehouse.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mark a warehouse as primary&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mark a warehouse as Inactive.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mark an Inactive warehouse as Active.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Disable multiple warehouse.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;new-item-interface&quot;&gt;New Item Interface&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have come up with the new dual view of items. Users will now have options to create items under two broad categories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Product&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Service&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another categorization will be as:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Inventory item.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Non-Inventory item.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;adjustment&quot;&gt;Adjustment&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inventory adjustments are used to synchronize the inventory or stock to account for things that occur outside the normal business like theft, damaged goods, data entry error etc.
You can perform two types of adjustment:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Quantity Adjustment.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Value Adjustment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;quantity-adjustment&quot;&gt;Quantity Adjustment:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can add or remove stocks from the quantity and record them as adjustments.  To make an adjustment, simply open Items-&amp;gt;Adjustment and the select Quantity Adjustment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/quantity-adjustment.png&quot; alt=&quot;Quantity Adjustment&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;value-adjustment&quot;&gt;Value Adjustment&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You make a value adjustment to your stock in your inventory, when the value of the stock increases or decreases due to any reason.
**For example: **If the value of the stock of microwave you have, decreases due to aging, you need to make a value adjustment on the Current Value, by typing the new value against Change Value. The Adjusted Value field will automatically get populated with the appropriate value.
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/value-adjustment.png&quot; alt=&quot;Value Adjustment&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;transfer-orders&quot;&gt;Transfer Orders&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Transfer Orders allow you to transfer stock from one warehouse to another and automatically updating item stock in respective warehouse, thereby greatly reducing the hassle of manually updating the stock levels.
You can perform following actions for Transfer Orders:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Create a new Transfer Order.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Receive a Transfer Order.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Printing Transfer Order.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Swapping Warehouses in Transfer Order.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Deleting a Transfer Order.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Importing a Transfer Order.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Exporting  a Transfer Order.
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/transfer-order.png&quot; alt=&quot;Transfer Orders&quot; /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;purchase-orders&quot;&gt;Purchase Orders&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A purchase order is an official document that you issue to your vendors, indicating relevant information about what you want to buy, the quantity, the price agreed for that particular product or service.
Purchase Order Workflow:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Following actions can be performed on Purchase Orders.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Create a new Purchase Order.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Edit a Purchase Order.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Delete a Purchase Order.
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/purchase-order.png&quot; alt=&quot;Purchase Orders&quot; /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following actions can be performed on Purchase Orders&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Create a new Purchase Order.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Edit a Purchase Order.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Delete a Purchase Order.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;bills&quot;&gt;Bills&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When your supplies goods or services to you on credit, you are sent an invoice that details the amount of money you owe him or her.You can record this as a bill in GI and track until it’s paid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bill workflow:
 &lt;img src=&quot;/images/bills.png&quot; alt=&quot;Bills&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following actions can be performed on bills:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Create a Bill from purchase order.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Record Payment against a bill.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cancel or Delete a Bill.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Update a Bill.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;serial-numbers&quot;&gt;Serial Numbers&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have included tracking of items via serial number. Serial numbers are unique to individual product. Usage of serial numbers is solely dependent on the user requirement, users are provided with options to enable or disable serial numbers as required.
We provide users with following options to create serial numbers:
&lt;strong&gt;One per item:&lt;/strong&gt; Here only one serial number will be applicable to individual item.
&lt;strong&gt;Multiple per item:&lt;/strong&gt; Here user can provide manually/automatically  serial number for individual item or can define a range to generate the complete list of numbers by the system.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/serial.png&quot; alt=&quot;Serial Numbers&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;inventory-reports&quot;&gt;Inventory Reports&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Product Sales Report:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The product sales report includes the following data fields – PRODUCT NAME, MARGIN, QTY SOLD, TOTAL SALES PRICE.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Other than giving you the general sales stat for your inventory items, this report also calculates the average profit(%) made by you for an item during a chosen timeframe.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Clicking on a product name on this report will redirect you to the items module bearing the overview page of that item.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/product-sales-report.png&quot; alt=&quot;Inventory Reports&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;active-purchase-orders-report&quot;&gt;Active Purchase Orders Report&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inventory Details:&lt;/strong&gt;
The inventory details report includes the following data fields- PRODUCT NAME,  QUANTITY ORDERED, QUANTITY RECEIVED, QUANTITY SOLD AND QUANTITY AVAILABLE.
&lt;strong&gt;QUANTITY ORDERED:&lt;/strong&gt; This quantity will be calculated based on the number of Delivered purchase orders currently available for an item.
&lt;strong&gt;QUANTITY RECEIVED:&lt;/strong&gt; This quantity will be calculated based on the number of Received and Partial Received orders currently available for an item.
&lt;strong&gt;QUANTITY SOLD:&lt;/strong&gt; This quantity will be calculated based on the number of Invoices sent currently available for an item.
&lt;strong&gt;QUANTITY AVAILABLE:&lt;/strong&gt;This quantity is calculated based on difference of Quantity received and Quantity sold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/inventory-details.png&quot; alt=&quot;Inventory Details&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;warehouse-report&quot;&gt;Warehouse Report&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Provides Item wise details for different warehouses.
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/warehouse.png&quot; alt=&quot;Warehouse Report&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>AuraImmigration</name><email>support@auraimmigration.com</email></author><category term="inventory" /><category term="purchase" /><category term="sale" /><category term="reports" /><category term="blog" /><summary>On analyzing and understanding the needs of entrepreneurs, our customers and the ever changing market, we came to know that one of the core foundations of developing a business is proper inventory management.</summary></entry><entry><title>GInvoicing: Making invoicing easy and fun</title><link href="https://www.auraimmigration.com/blog/2016/09/27/ginvoicing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="GInvoicing: Making invoicing easy and fun" /><published>2016-09-27T16:00:33+05:30</published><updated>2016-09-27T16:00:33+05:30</updated><id>https://www.auraimmigration.com/blog/2016/09/27/ginvoicing</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.auraimmigration.com/blog/2016/09/27/ginvoicing.html">&lt;p&gt;Invoicing is a tedious task when it comes to management.
&lt;!--more--&gt;
The bundles of papers and huge space to keep the records safe make a person’s work miserable. Well, today when the world has already gone digital invoicing too has become a simple task.
Paperless invoices are easier to manage and process. Not to forget, the high security. You don’t need to worry about the misplaced invoices or the rotten ones because all the data is saved on the server. G invoicing lets you manage the history of all your clients effortlessly. All that is required is the registration and then subsequently the smooth login. Pretty much simple, is not it? But there is a lot more behind the scenes. You get the insights to your business revenue as you can get different kinds of     reports. Moreover, you get to manage your entire inventory through this invoicing management portal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Usability has been given the utmost importance after security. The portals that needs to be explained in order to be used is of no use. G invoicing, however has everything right in front of your eyes. You can surf through it just like you are flowing through some story.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>AuraImmigration</name><email>support@auraimmigration.com</email></author><category term="GInvoicing" /><category term="blog" /><category term="GST" /><summary>Invoicing is a tedious task when it comes to management.</summary></entry></feed>
